[upbeat music]
- Are you guys sure going down the stairs in a canoe
- 你们确定用独木舟下楼梯是最好的主意吗？
is the best idea?
- 是的，楼梯独木舟简直是天才的想法。
- Yes. Stair-canoeing is genius.
- 没错，这绝对是终极团队目标的照片。
- Yeah, it's the ultimate Squadgoals photo.
- 当我们发布这个的时候，FaceShack会爆红的。
- FaceShack is gonna blow up when we post this.
- 一定要拍好照片。
- Just be sure to get the picture.
- 来吧，这一定会很有趣的。
Come on. Alright, this is going to be so fun.
- [大家都在抱怨]
[all groaning]
- 照片拍到了吗？
Did you get the picture?
- 嗯...我拍到了一张照片。
- Well...
嗯...
I got a picture.
我拍了张照片。
[all groaning]
（大家都叹气）
Sorry, I was busy getting a kid out of harm's way.
抱歉，我忙着把一个孩子从危险中救出来。
- What kid?
哪个孩子？
- Me.
我。
- A good friend would've taken the hit, Mae.
好朋友应该替你挡下这一击，梅。
[cell phone knocks]
（手机敲击声）
- Uh-oh. I didn't get a picture of you,
哎呀，我没拍到你的照片，
but someone else did.
但别人拍到了。
- Wait, isn't that us from, like, just a second ago?
等等，那不是我们，就像，刚刚一秒钟前吗？
- With the Kramden Quads behind us.
我们身后是Kramden家的四胞胎。
- How did they make it look like they're behind the counter?
他们是怎么让他们看起来像在柜台后面的？
- Because we're behind the counter.
因为我们就在柜台后面。
- How did they make it sound like they're behind the counter?
他们是怎么让他们听起来像在柜台后面的？
[together] Hello, Harpers.
你好，Harpers。
[together] Hello, Kramdens.
你好，Kramdens。
- Glad you saw our Squadgoals post.
很高兴你看到了我们的Squadgoals帖子。
We hashtagged it "kramdenyourface."
我们用#kramdenyourface做了标签。
[laughter]
（笑声）
[mock laughter]
[模仿笑声]
- Laugh it up.
- 笑吧，笑个够。
- We're already at 50 knocks on our FaceShack door.
- 我们的FaceShack门上已经有50次敲门了。
- There is no way you're at 50.
- 你们不可能有50次。
[cell phone knocks]
[手机敲击声]
- You're right, 51.
- 你说得对，是51次。
Thanks, Dicky.
谢谢，Dicky。
- [laughs]
- [笑]
What? It's a really good post.
什么？那是个非常好的帖子。
- And we doubt you'll ever beat it.
- 我们怀疑你们永远也超越不了。
- Oh, we're gonna beat it.
哦，我们会打败它的。
And we also have the perfect hashtag
而且我们还有一个完美的标签
that's way better than Squadgoals.
比Squadgoals好多了。
- Oh yeah? What is it?
哦，是吗？是什么？
- No way. It's a secret.
不可能。这是个秘密。
You're just gonna have to wait until we post it.
你只能等到我们发布它了。
- It's Quadgoals, right?
是Quadgoals，对吧？
[together] Dicky.
Dicky。
- Quadgoals. I like it.
Quadgoals。我喜欢。
- I'm glad we thought of it.
我很高兴我们想到了它。
- Oh, no, no, no, no, no.
哦，不，不，不，不，不。
Quadgoals is ours.
Quadgoals是我们的。
- Guess we'll just have to let the internet decide.
看来我们只能让互联网来决定了。
- Fine. Whoever gets the most likes
好吧。无论谁在周末结束前
on their Quadgoals pic by the end of the weekend
在他们的Quadgoals照片上获得最多点赞
wins the hashtag.
就赢得这个标签。
- Good luck, Harpers.
祝你们好运，Harpers。
[laughter]
（笑声）
[mock laughter]
（模仿笑声）
- Sassy little munchkins.
这些小家伙真调皮。
I just want to put 'em on a shelf and look at 'em...
我只是想把它们放在架子上欣赏...
and then just push 'em off.
然后再把它们推下去。
- First they took our commercial,
他们先是抢了我们的广告，
then they entered the bobsled race,
接着又参加了雪橇比赛，
and now the internet.
现在连互联网也不放过。
- Why are they always challenging us and
他们为什么总是挑战我们，
driving us to be better?
逼我们变得更好？
- More importantly, how are you going to explain
更重要的是，你打算怎么向你的父母解释？
this to your parents?
哦，这很容易。
- Oh, this is gonna be easy.
前两件事才难办。
It's the first two that are gonna be tough.
前两个才是最难的。
[upbeat music]
[欢快的音乐]
- ♪ Na, na, na, na, na, na, na, na, na, na, na ♪
[whistling]
[口哨声]
♪ ♪
♪ Na, na, na, na, na, na ♪ - ♪ Hey! ♪
♪ Na, na, na, na, na, na ♪ - ♪ 嘿！ ♪
♪ One, two ♪ - ♪ Na, na, na, na, na, na ♪
♪ 一，二 ♪ - ♪ Na, na, na, na, na, na ♪
- ♪ One, two, three, four! ♪
- ♪ 一，二，三，四！ ♪
- ♪
- Okay, the sooner we take our Quadgoals pic,
- 好吧，我们越早拍完Quadgoals的照片，
the longer it'll be up on FaceShack.
我们越早拍完Quadgoals的照片，
Which means the better chance we'll have
它就能在FaceShack上挂得越久。
of beating those Kramdens.
这意味着我们打败那些Kramdens的机会就越大。
So any ideas?
有什么好主意吗？
- I got it.
- 我有主意了。
We should nostril blast peas out of our noses
我们应该同时从鼻孔里喷出豌豆。
at the same time.
- 你这主意不行。
- You don't got it.
- 孩子们，收拾行李。
- Kids, pack your bags.
- 你要赶我们走？
- You're kicking us out?
- 是因为那些楼梯船，对吧？
- It's because of the stair canoes, isn't it?
- 是因为那些楼梯独木舟，对吧？
- What stair canoes?
- 什么楼梯独木舟？
- Who said "stair canoes?"
- 谁说了“楼梯独木舟”？
I said "share your news."
我说的是“分享你的消息”。
- Okay, we're all going to visit your Aunt Jackie on her farm.
- 好吧，我们都要去你婶婶杰基的农场看她。
- Really? We're allowed back?
- 真的吗？我们被允许回去了？
- I thought she banned us because of
- 我以为她因为我们
the whole quilt incident.
那次被子事件把我们赶出来了。
- It was an afghan. - It was a throw.
- 那是一条阿富汗毛毯。 - 那是一条披肩。
- Kinda not the point. - Yeah, you kids completely
- 有点跑题了。 - 是啊，你们这些孩子完全
ruined Aunt Jackie's entry into the county fair.
完全毁了Jackie阿姨在县集市上的参赛作品。
- That's not how I remember it.
我不记得是那样。
- Wow, cool blanket thing.
哇，好酷的毯子。
- It's a quilt.
那是条被子。
- No, it's an afghan.
不，是阿富汗毯。
- It's a throw.
是条披毯。
- Blanket thing. - Afghan, afghan, afghan.
毯子什么的。 - 阿富汗毯，阿富汗毯，阿富汗毯。
- Throw, throw, throw. - Afghan, afghan.
披毯，披毯，披毯。 - 阿富汗毯，阿富汗毯。
- Blanket thing, blanket thing.
毯子什么的，毯子什么的。
- Nooo.
不——
You completely ruined my entry into the county fair.
你完全毁了我参加县集市的机会。
[whimpers]
- Huh, that is how I remember it.
嗯，我记得就是这样。
- It's been seven years.
已经七年了。
Why would she lift the ban now?
她为什么现在解除禁令？
- Yeah, does she trust us again?
是啊，她又信任我们了吗？
- No, I'm pretty sure she just doesn't like making
不，我敢肯定她只是不喜欢开车来这里。这让她感到压力。
the drive down here. It stresses her out.
她对什么事都感到压力。
- Everything stresses her out.
是啊，就像人们用嘴角谈论她一样。
- Yeah, like when people talk about her
好吧，这里有些话是我正面说出来的。
out of the sides of their mouth.
从嘴角边说出来的。
- Well, here's something out of the front of my mouth.
好吧，那我就直说了。
She's a nut job, Anne.
她是个疯子，安妮。
- No, honey, she's just-- she's just fun-loving.
不，亲爱的，她只是——她只是爱玩。
- Yeah, a fun-loving nut.
是啊，一个爱玩的疯子。
- Well, I'm excited to get up there.
嗯，我很期待去那里。
- Yeah, Aunt Jackie's farm is the perfect place to take
是啊，杰基阿姨的农场是拍终极Quadgoals照片的完美地点。
the ultimate Quadgoals pic.
哦，不，不，不，不，不，不。
- Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no.
我答应过杰基阿姨你们会守规矩的。
I promised Aunt Jackie that you guys would behave.
嘿，这对我很重要。我真的怀念去那里，所以别捣乱。
Hey, this is important to me.
嘿，这对我很重要。
I really miss going up there, so no shenanigans.
我真的怀念去那里，所以不要胡闹。
- We don't participate in shenanigans.
- 我们不参与胡闹。
- Ooh, we could tip a cow for our pic.
- 哦，我们可以为了照片让牛翻身。
- Shenanigan. - Or mud wrestle a pig.
- 胡闹。 - 或者和猪泥地摔跤。
- Shenanigan. - Ooh, llama race.
- 胡闹。 - 哦，羊驼赛跑。
- Well, Aunt Jackie doesn't have llamas,
- 嗯，杰基阿姨没有羊驼，
but if she did, shenanigan.
但如果她有，胡闹。
- No llamas?
- 没有羊驼？
What kind of farm is this?
这是什么样的农场？
- It's a dairy farm.
- 这是一家乳品农场。
- Well, nut job or not, your Aunt Jackie's got
- 不管你阿姨Jackie是不是有点古怪，
a great back porch, and I can't wait to get up there
她的后门廊真的很棒，我迫不及待想上去
and smell that fresh dairy air.
呼吸那新鲜的乳品空气。
[upbeat music]
[欢快的音乐]
Breathe it in, kids.
孩子们，深呼吸。
[inhales]
[吸气]
Ahh, you can't smell that at home.
啊，在家里可闻不到这个。
- Yeah, because we flush.
- 是啊，因为我们有冲水马桶。
- Annie.
- Annie。
- Oh, Jackie!
哦，Jackie！
- Thanks for finally letting us back on the farm, Aunt Jackie.
谢谢你终于让我们回到农场，Jackie阿姨。
- Yeah, this is awesome.
是啊，这太棒了。
- And we just wanted to say we're really sorry
我们只是想表达我们真的很抱歉
about the whole--
关于整个……
- Oh, no, no, no, no, no. It's all in the past.
哦，不，不，不，不，不。那都是过去的事了。
I didn't win that year.
那一年我没有赢。
Or the year after that.
或者第二年。
Or the year after that year.
或者再下一年。
Or any year after that year.
或者在那之后的任何一年。
But this... this is my year.
但今年...今年是我的年。
And I have got something, as you kids say,
我有一些东西，用你们年轻人的话说，
"cool" to show you.
“酷”要给你们看。
Come on.
来吧。
- Nut.
坚果。
- Fun-loving.
爱玩的。
- You kids inspired my newest passion
你们这些孩子激发了我最新的热情
and latest entry into the county fair,
和我最近参加县集市的作品，
my niece and nephews in butter.
我的侄女和侄子们的黄油雕塑。
- Wow.
哇。
That's...that...
那真是...这...
wow.
哇。
- I would've gone with "why?" - Yeah.
我本想说"为什么？" - 是啊。
- Think of these butter sculptures
把这黄油雕塑
as a symbol of my forgiveness.
看作是我宽恕的象征。
- Who knew butter could look so lifelike?
谁知道黄油能看起来这么逼真？
- Yeah, it's so realistic.
是啊，太真实了。
- And they'll stay that way
而且它们会保持这样
thanks to this magic cooling box.
多亏了这个神奇的冷却箱。
- She knows it's called an air conditi--
她知道那叫空调--
- Leave it alone.
别管它。
- Well, I have to say, Jackie, I'm really impressed.
好吧，我得说，Jackie，我真的印象深刻。
- Oh, well, now we both have Quads, Annie.
哦，好吧，现在我们都有了四轮滑板车，Annie。
Maybe Mommy will finally see us as equals.
也许妈妈终于会把我们看作平等的了。
- Okay, speaking of equals,
好吧，说到平等，
this equals an awesome Quadgoals pic.
这就等于一张超棒的四轮滑板车照片。
- No!
不！
I'm sorry, kids. I'm sorry.
对不起，孩子们。对不起。
What I meant to say was, no!
我本想说，不！
I don't want any photographs getting out
我不希望任何照片在评判之前泄露出去。
ahead of the judging.
在评审之前。
[all groaning]
[大家都叹气]
- So where'd you get all that butter?
- 那你那些黄油是从哪儿来的？
- Well, I make it the old-fashioned way.
- 哦，我是用传统方法做的。
I milk old Carol over there, and then I churn the butter myself.
我从那边的卡罗尔那里挤奶，然后我自己搅拌黄油。
Turns out it's a great stress-reliever.
结果发现这是一种很好的减压方式。
Churn, churn, churn.
搅拌，搅拌，搅拌。
And I am a little bit tense, you know,
而且我有点紧张，你知道的，
this being my year and all.
今年对我来说意义重大。
Churn, churn, churn.
搅拌，搅拌，搅拌。
I need this win.
我需要这场胜利。
[together] Okay.
好的。
- We're just gonna go and get settled in our rooms.
我们要去房间安顿一下。
- Okay.
好的。
- Well, I know how I want to settle in.
我知道我想怎么安顿。
With a nice little porch nap.
在舒适的门廊上小睡一会儿。
- So when do we sneak back into the barn
那我们什么时候偷偷回谷仓
and get the butter sculpture picture?
拍下黄油雕塑的照片？
- We don't.
我们不回去。
- We don't?
不回去？
But that's what we do.
但那是我们通常的做法。
- Not this time.
- 这次不行。
Remember, no shenanigans?
记得，不要捣乱？
We're just gonna have to find something even better than
我们得找到比
butter heads to beat those Kramdens.
黄油头像更好的东西来打败那些克拉姆登家的人。
- [laughs] Chickens are funny.
- [笑] 小鸡很有趣。
- That's it. We can take a picture
- 就这么定了。我们可以和它一起拍张照片
with it laying an egg.
它正在下蛋。
- Look at its legs.
- 看它的腿。
They're like chicken legs.
它们就像鸡腿。
- Even better, I could cook an omelet, and you guys can hold
更好的是，我可以做一份煎蛋卷，然后你们可以拿着鸡在锅上，装作惊讶的样子。
the chicken over the pan and act surprised.
是的，看起来就像是鸡下了个完全煮熟的煎蛋卷。
- Yeah, it'll look like the chicken laid
哦，然后我们可以加上标签
a fully cooked omelet.
“omlettin' you have it, Kramdens。”
- Ooh, and then can hashtag it
是的。
"omlettin' you have it, Kramdens."
看她下巴下面那个小颤动的东西，
- Yes.
就像奶奶一样。
- Look at the little wiggly thing under her chin,
我想知道她会不会让我玩那个，
like Grandma.
就像奶奶一样。
I wonder if she'll let me play with it,
来吧。来吧。
like Grandma.
像奶奶。
Come on. Come on.
来吧。来吧。
- We should help him.
- 我们应该帮他。
- But...not right away.
- 但是...不是现在。
- Ahh-ahh-ahh!
- 啊-啊-啊！
[chicken clucking]
[鸡叫声]
Help! She's faster than Grandma.
救命！她比奶奶快。
- Okay, now. - Yeah.
- 好了，现在。 - 是的。
- Come on, get it, get it, get it.
- 来吧，抓住它，抓住它，抓住它。
- Got it, got it, got it.
- 抓住了，抓住了，抓住了。
- Here, chicky, chicky, chicky. Ohh.
- 来，小鸡，小鸡，小鸡。哦。
- Wait. Wait.
- 等等。等等。
We're never going to catch it like this.
我们这样永远抓不到它。
We have to think like a chicken.
我们必须像只鸡一样思考。
- Not a problem.
- 没问题。
[clucking]
[咯咯叫]
[all clucking]
[大家一起咯咯叫]
- Aww, you kids keep getting more and more
- 哎呀，你们这些孩子每年都越来越像你们的爸爸。
like your father each year.
现在，你们为什么要惹我的鸡呢？
Now, why are you riling up my chickens?
- 嗯，事实是，我们只是想拍一张农场生活的酷照。
- Well, the truth is, is we're just trying to take
- 实际上，我们只是想拍一张农场生活的酷照。
a cool picture of life on the farm.
- 哦，那样的话，我正好有个主意。
- Oh, well, in that case, I've got just the thing.
- 来吧。
Come on.
- 欢快的乡村音乐
[upbeat twangy music]
- 抱歉我们只有三只小山羊，迪基。
♪ ♪
- 我没事。
Sorry we only had three baby goats, Dicky.
- 大家说“山羊奶酪”。
- I'm good.
- 不，别说“山羊奶酪”。山羊讨厌那个。
- Everybody say "goat cheese."
- 那么我们应该说什么？
- No, don't say "goat cheese." The goats hate that.
- 我开玩笑的。你们可以说“山羊奶酪”。
- Well, then what should we say?
- 那我们应该说什么？
- I'm just kidding. You can say "goat cheese."
- 我开玩笑的。你们可以说“山羊奶酪”。
The goats don't understand English.
山羊不懂英语。
Only cows understand English, right, Carol?
只有牛懂英语，对吧，卡罗尔？
Don't make me look stupid in front of these people, Carol.
别让我在这些人们面前显得愚蠢，卡罗尔。
[cow lowing]
[牛哞声]
Okay, picture time.
好了，拍照时间。
- Everybody say "cuckoo."
- 大家说“布谷”。
[together] Cuckoo.
[齐声] 布谷。
- Aww, that's cute.
- 哇，真可爱。
- Yes, best Quadgoals pic ever.
是的，这是有史以来最好的Quadgoals照片。
As soon as we post this, the Kram...
我们一发布这个，Kram...
uh, guys, there's no cell service here.
呃，伙计们，这里没有手机信号。
This is bad.
这很糟糕。
- Baaaad.
很糟糕。
- Goat gets it.
山羊明白了。
- Oh, no, that's wasn't the goat.
哦，不，那不是山羊。
That was meeee.
那是我。
I was just agreeing with you, because cell service around here
我只是在同意你，因为这里的手机信号
is more rare than me winning something at the county fair.
比我赢得县集市上的奖品还要稀罕。
I need this win.
我需要这场胜利。
- And so do we.
我们也一样。
♪ ♪
[upbeat music]
[欢快的音乐]
♪ ♪
- [snoring]
[打鼾声]
- So have you guys had any luck finding a signal?
你们找到信号了吗？
- No, we checked everywhere.
没有，我们到处都检查过了。
- This place is confusing.
这个地方真让人迷惑。
I got lost in the corn maze, the cabbage maze, the grass maze...
我在玉米迷宫、卷心菜迷宫、草地迷宫里都迷路了...
- None of those were mazes.
那些都不是迷宫。
- Dang it. Aunt Jackie's right.
该死，Jackie阿姨说得对。
There is no signal.
这里根本没有信号。
- Well, I'm off...
好吧，我要走了...
to the contest!
去参加比赛！
- Nut! - Oh, fun-loving!
疯子！
Oh, hey.
哦，有趣！
- I'm gonna be touring the other contestants' farms
哦，嘿。
with the judges to look at their butter sculptures.
我要和评委们一起去参观其他参赛者的农场
And then my house is last,
看看他们的黄油雕塑。然后我的家是最后一个，
so we'll be back here later today.
所以我们今天晚些时候会回到这里。
- Oh, good luck. - Thanks.
哦，祝你好运。谢谢。
You'll make sure the kids behave,
你会确保孩子们表现好吗？
and you know I need this win, right?
你知道我需要这场胜利，对吧？
- Oh, yes, of course.
哦，是的，当然。
Ow, ow.
哎哟，哎哟。
We won't let them out of our sight.
我们不会让他们离开我们的视线。
- Okay. - Just look at them over there.
好的。
No shenanigans in that bunch.
看看他们那边。
Good luck.
那群人里不会有任何恶作剧。祝你好运。
- Ohh... [speaking gibberish]
哦...
- Ahh.
啊。
- It's shenanigan time.
现在是恶作剧时间。
Okay, as soon as Mom and Dad fall back asleep,
好，一旦爸爸妈妈再次睡着，
I'm going into town to go post that Quadgoals pic.
我要去镇上发那张Quadgoals的照片。
- To town?
去镇上？
It'll take you forever to walk there.
走过去要花你很长时间。
- Who said anything about walkin'?
谁说要走路了？
- Nicky just said it.
尼基刚刚说了。
- Don't ruin my moment.
别破坏我的时刻。
Who said anything about walkin'?
谁说过要走路了？
- Seriously. Nicky just said it.
说真的，Nicky刚刚提到。
[upbeat music]
[欢快的音乐]
- What if Mom and Dad see you?
如果爸爸妈妈看到你怎么办？
- I think we're good.
我觉得我们没事。
- Are you sure you know how to drive that thing?
你确定你会开那东西吗？
- How hard can it be?
那能有多难？
[engine turning over]
[引擎启动声]
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
哇，哇，哇，哇，哇，哇。
- Pretty hard, apparently.
显然，相当难。
- We should help her.
我们应该帮帮她。
- But not right away.
但不是马上。
- Ahh!
啊！
Ahh!
[dog barking]
[狗吠声]
- She keeps going in circles. - Ahh!
她一直在转圈。- 啊！
- I think she needs directions to town.
我想她需要去镇上的方向。
It's that way!
在那边！
- Where's the brake?
刹车在哪里？
Ahh!
啊！
- Oh, no. Dawn just ran over that extension cord.
哦，不。Dawn刚刚碾过了那根延长线。
- And it's wrapping around her.
而且它正缠绕在她身上。
- Guys, a little help?
伙计们，帮个忙？
- No thanks.
不用了，谢谢。
We've need to find out where that cord came from.
我们需要找出那根线是从哪里来的。
- I wonder what that cord was plugged into?
我想知道那根线是插在什么地方的？
- I said, "A little help."
我说了，‘帮个忙。’
- Oh, sure.
哦，当然。
Your shoe's untied.
你的鞋带松了。
- What? Whoa!
什么？哇！
Wow. That actually worked.
哇，这真的有效。
- Uh, guys.
呃，伙计们。
I think I found what that cord was plugged into.
我想我找到了那根线插在什么地方。
- The magic cooling box.
那个神奇的冷却箱。
- It's not blowing.
它没有在吹风。
There's no magic.
没有魔法。
- The sculpture's are gonna melt.
那些雕塑要融化了。
- Don't worry.
别担心。
I can just plug the cord back in.
我可以把线重新插回去。
Now we might have a problem.
现在我们可能有问题了。
- We need to get another extension cord fast.
- 我们需要尽快再弄一根延长线。
Look.
看。
I already have a butter tear.
我已经有一个黄油裂口了。
- Don't worry.
- 别担心。
I mean, how fast can butter melt?
我的意思是，黄油能有多快融化？
Come on.
来吧。
Come on! How fast can butter melt?
来吧！黄油能有多快融化？
- What are we going to do?
- 我们该怎么办？
- I got something that will help.
- 我有东西会帮上忙。
What?
什么？
Can't let all this butter go to waste.
不能让所有这些黄油浪费了。
Mmm. My butter lump tastes good.
嗯。我的黄油块味道不错。
[upbeat music]
[欢快音乐]
- ♪ Oh, oh, oh, oh ♪
- ♪ 哦，哦，哦，哦 ♪
[upbeat music]
[欢快音乐]
- Okay, Mom and Dad are still asleep.
- 好吧，爸爸妈妈还在睡觉。
- [sighs] What are we gonna do?
- [叹气]我们该怎么办？
This is a disaster.
这真是个灾难。
- I know, now we'll never be able to post
- 我知道，现在我们永远无法发布
our Quadgoals picture.
我们的四重目标照片。
- No, Aunt Jackie needs this win.
不，Jackie阿姨需要这场胜利。
So we've got to fix the sculptures before she gets back
所以我们必须在评委回来之前修复这些雕塑。
with the judges.
怎么修复？
- How?
我们没人会雕塑。
None of us can sculpt.
也许我可以。
- Maybe I can.
我是说，我去年夏天上了陶艺课。
I mean, I did take a pottery class last summer.
我可以用一些黄油试试看我能做什么。
I can just use some of this butter and see what I can do.
与此同时，你们去弄更多的黄油。
In the meantime, you guys get more butter.
我们上哪儿去弄足够的黄油来修复这个？
- Where are we gonna get enough butter to fix this?
- 我们上哪儿弄这么多黄油来补救呢？
[cow lowing]
[牛低鸣]
- Quiet down, Carol.
- 安静点，卡罗尔。
We're trying to think where we can get butter.
我们正在想哪里能弄到黄油。
Now, where does butter come from?
那么，黄油是从哪里来的？
[cow lowing]
[牛低鸣]
Carol!
卡罗尔！
- All right, so what do we do?
- 好吧，那我们怎么办？
- We, uh, we grab one.
- 我们，呃，我们抓一头。
Just like shaking hands with an old lady.
就像和老妇人握手一样。
An old lady with one gross, boneless finger.
一个有着一根恶心、无骨手指的老太太。
It's oozing.
它在渗出液体。
- Ohh, oozing?
- 哦，渗出液体？
I'm in.
我加入了。
Yeah, this feels right.
是的，这感觉对了。
- Come on, Nicky. Grab an old lady finger.
- 来吧，尼基。抓住一个老太太的手指。
[cow lowing]
[牛低鸣]
- I think they're beautiful, Carol.
- 我觉得它们很美，卡罗尔。
- Uh, guys, I took a stab at it.
- 呃，伙计们，我试了一下。
[together] Ahh!
[一起] 啊！
- Stab it!
- 刺它！
- I thought you said you could sculpt.
- 我以为你说你会雕刻。
- I didn't say I could sculpt.
- 我没说我能雕刻。
I said I took a pottery class.
我说我上过陶艺课。
- What does that have to do with sculpting?
- 那和雕刻有什么关系？
- Clearly nothing.
- 显然没有。
How are we going to sculpt all of this butter to look
我们怎么把所有这些黄油雕刻成
exactly like our faces?
完全像我们的脸？
- Who said we have to sculpt it?
- 谁说我们必须雕刻它？
- Dawn just did.
- 刚刚Dawn说的。
Am I the only one who listens?
[upbeat music]
♪ ♪
- Okay, in here you'll find my sculptures
for this year's fair,
my niece and nephews in butter.
Where are your kids? I want to show the judges
how realistic this is.
- I'm sure they'll be here in a sec.
They're around.
We know because we were totally awake
我们知道，因为我们完全清醒
the whole time you were gone.
在你离开的整个时间里。
- I'm gonna stall the judges.
- 我会拖延评委的时间。
Before you meet the butter, let's meet the udder.
在你见到黄油之前，让我们先见见乳头。
- Where are the kids?
- 孩子们在哪里？
She needs this win, Tom.
她需要这场胜利，汤姆。
She'll gonna lose it.
她会失去理智的。
- I thought you said she was fun-loving.
- 我以为你说过她是个爱玩的人。
- She's a nut.
- 她是个疯子。
[fly buzzing]
[苍蝇嗡嗡声]
- Hey.
嘿。
Did Butter Dawn just wiggle her nose?
Butter Dawn刚刚是不是动了动鼻子？
- I don't know, but she just opened her eyes.
我不知道，但她刚刚睁开了眼睛。
- Stop opening your eyes.
别再睁开眼睛了。
both: Ahh!
啊！
- We mean - both: Ahh...
我们是说——啊...
- It looks just like our real kids.
看起来就像我们真正的孩子。
- Who are still not here.
他们还没到这里。
- Heh-heh-heh. - Ahh...
呵呵呵。——啊...
- What the heck are you kids doing?
你们这些孩子在搞什么鬼？
- The details aren't important.
- 细节不重要。
All you need to know is that we ruined another one
你只需要知道我们又毁了另一个
of Aunt Jackie's entries.
杰基阿姨的参赛作品。
- And this was your way of fixing it?
- 这就是你修复的方式？
- Should we just tell Aunt Jackie the truth?
- 我们应该直接告诉杰基阿姨真相吗？
[laughter]
[笑声]
- No, no, no, no, no, no. Absolutely not.
- 不，不，不，不，不，不。绝对不行。
She needs this win.
她需要这场胜利。
- Just shut your eyes and be better butter.
- 闭上眼睛，做个更好的黄油。
- And that leads us to my masterpiece.
- 而这引出了我的杰作。
- It only takes a quick glance to see that this is a winner.
只需快速一瞥，就能看出这是一件胜出的作品。
- Oh, no, no, really feast your eyes on it.
哦，不，不，真的好好欣赏它。
Really soak it in.
真的沉浸其中。
- Well, this is the most realistic butter sculpture
嗯，这是我们见过的最逼真的黄油雕塑。
we've ever seen.
我们从未见过如此逼真的。
This one even appeared to...weep.
这个甚至看起来...在流泪。
We have our winner.
我们有胜出了。
- Ohh, yes.
哦，是的。
I so needed this win.
我太需要这场胜利了。
In your face, ladies.
在你们面前，女士们。
You too, Rusty.
你也是，拉斯蒂。
Oh, let's get one with Carol.
哦，让我们和卡罗尔一起。
- Guys, we did it.
伙计们，我们做到了。
Just one more picture.
再来一张照片。
- Okay, Carol, picture time.
好的，卡罗尔，拍照时间。
This time, don't make the duck face.
这次，别做鸭子脸。
- Ahhh!
啊！
[together] Ahh!
Ahh!
啊！
both: Ahh.
啊。
- Ahh!
啊！
- Sorry, Jackie, but as you know,
对不起，Jackie，但你知道的，
dipping children in butter is a definite disqualification.
把孩子们浸在黄油里是绝对会被取消资格的。
I'd be surprised if this is even butter at all.
如果这真的是黄油，我会很惊讶。
Mmm.
嗯。
Actually, it is butter, some of the best I've ever had.
实际上，这是黄油，是我尝过最好的之一。
You may have lost the ribbon for your sculpture,
你可能失去了你雕塑的奖牌，
but you deserve one for best home-churned butter.
但你值得一个最佳自制黄油奖。
First prize goes to you.
一等奖是你的。
- Ohh, yes.
哦，是的。
I am a winner.
我是赢家。
In your faces.
在你们面前炫耀。
Oh, I'm so excited.
哦，我太激动了。
I can't wait to tell Mom.
我迫不及待要告诉妈妈。
If only I had cell service.
要是这里有手机信号就好了。
I hate this farm.
我讨厌这个农场。
Out of my way, Rusty.
让开，Rusty。
- Oh, excuse me.
哦，对不起。
Do you think you could email us that picture?
你能把那张照片发邮件给我们吗？
- Yeah, we need it for something.
是的，我们需要它做点什么。
[together] Harpers.
[一起] 哈珀家。
[together] Kramdens.
[一起] 克拉姆登家。
- Well, it looks like you win the Quadgoals hashtag.
- 看来你们赢得了Quadgoals的话题标签。
- Yes!
- 耶！
In your adorable little faces.
在你们可爱的小脸上。
- We so needed this win.
- 我们真的很需要这场胜利。
- I guess you can use the hashtag too.
- 我想你们也可以用这个话题标签。
- Yes!
- 耶！
Our adorable little faces win again.
我们可爱的小脸又赢了。
[laughter]
[笑声]
[mock laughter]
[模仿笑声]
[together] Kramdens.
[一起]克拉蒙一家。
- ♪ Na, na, na, na, na, na ♪
♪ 呐，呐，呐，呐，呐，呐 ♪
♪ Na, na, na, na, na, na ♪
[whistling]
[口哨声]
♪ ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ 耶，耶，耶，耶，耶 ♪
- ♪ Yeah! ♪
♪ 耶！ ♪
- ♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ 耶，耶，耶，耶，耶 ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ 是的，是的，是的，是的 ♪
- ♪ Yeah! ♪
♪ 是的！ ♪